<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Maksym Prokopov personal blog</title>
    <link>https://prokopov.me/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Maksym Prokopov personal blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ru-Ru</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://prokopov.me/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Travel</title>
      <link>https://prokopov.me/pages/trips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2013 13:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prokopov.me/pages/trips/</guid>
      <description>Очень люблю Юго-Восточную Азию за теплый климат и прекрасных людей.
2022 Italy, Rome 5 days 2022 Montenegro, Djenovichi 1 week 2021 Spain, Villa Joiosa 1 week perfect family beach rest, 1 week more than enough 2020 Spain, Barcelona cancelled due to Corona-19 :( 2019-2020 Norway, Asker 2 weeks 2019 Germany, Freiburg 3 days 2019 Austria, Vienna 1 month 2019 Турция, пригород Анталии 1 неделя 2 weeks 2019 Germany, Berlin 3 days 2019 Sicily, gastrotour 6 days 2018-2019 Thailand, Koh Samui 6 months 2018 Italy (Toskana region), gastrotour 6 days 2018 Finland (Jyväskylä, Helsinki) 3 days 2018 Germany, Hamburg 3 days 2017 Germany, Mannheim, Stuttgart, Heidelberg 1 month 2016 Egypt (Hurgada), Turkey (Istanbul) 2013-2014 Thailand (Bangkok, Ayutaya, Patthaya) [Cambodia (Siam-Riep, Sehanukville, Battamband, Campot, Phnom Penh)] 2012 Malaysia (Kuala Lumpur, isl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read</title>
      <link>https://prokopov.me/pages/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prokopov.me/pages/reading/</guid>
      <description>My interests currently lie in the following categories:
Psyhology, self-improvement and mental health Domain Driven Design Lean production, lean services SRE and DevOps Here is my confession to the one of the greatest books about computer science:
Code: The Hidden Language of Computer Hardware and Software
if you are a computer science enthusiast, this is must read!
Стейнбек говорил, что «плохой роман должен развлекать читателей, средний – воздействовать на их чувства, а лучший – озарять им путь»</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create</title>
      <link>https://prokopov.me/pages/creating/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 07:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prokopov.me/pages/creating/</guid>
      <description>I beleive being creative is an essential part of being a human.
Before I got my first computer Intel 386 DX 40 in 1994, I used to write small programs using MK61 programmable calculator, then a bit of soviet Corvette computer programming at school. Since that time I didn&amp;rsquo;t stop my journey with software engineering, but nowadays with more focus towards DevOps and SRE practices.
My first book about software engineering was C++ by Bjarne Stroustrup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://prokopov.me/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prokopov.me/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Maksym Prokopov. These days I mostly involved in DevOps, Lean IT and IT services.
A long time ago I started by web developer career from PHP 3.0.3 and have used lots of technlologies and programming languages. Surprisingly, but I started using PHP for my job today again after almost 18 years. What a destiny!
Since 2006 I started using Ruby on Rails a lot. 2015 got addicted to Clojure and ClojureScript and did some production-ready things.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
